Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2015
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Percussionist Joe Desotelle with composer Steven Crane at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Steven Crane composer Joe Desotelle percussion.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_210.tif)
- Trumpeter Samuel Wells and composer Paul Hembree at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Paul Hembree composer Sanuel Wells Trumpet.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_211.tif)
- Trumpeter Samuel Wells performing Paul Hembree's Blue sky catastrophe at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Samuel Wells.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_212.tif)
- Trumpeter Samuel Wells performing Paul Hembree's Blue sky catastrophe at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Samuel Wells trumpet.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_213.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Rogewr Reynolds composer.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_214.tif)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0709.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_215.tif)
- Violinist Irvine Arditti and pianist Eric Huebner performing Elliott Carter's Duo for violin and piano at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-04, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Eric Huebner piano Irvine Arditti violin.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_216.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain conducting rehearsal of Jacob Druckman's Come around at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0734.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_217.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain conducting rehearsal of Jacob Druckman's Come around at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0735.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_218.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain conducting rehearsal of Jacob Druckman's Come around at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0738.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_219.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain conducting rehearsal of Jacob Druckman's Come around at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0742.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_220.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain conducting rehearsal of Jacob Druckman's Come around at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0743.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_221.tif)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and cellist Veronica Nettles performing Bernard Rands's Walcott songs at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0745.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_222.tif)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and cellist Veronica Nettles performing Bernard Rands's Walcott songs at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0748.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_223.tif)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and cellist Veronica Nettles performing Bernard Rands's Walcott songs at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0750.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_224.tif)
- Cellist Veronica Nettles with conductor Daniel Bassin at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0753.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_225.tif)
- Cellist Veronica Nettles with conductor Daniel Bassin at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0756.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_226.tif)
- Cellist Veronica Nettles with composer Augusta Read Thomas at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0760.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_227.tif)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley, cellist Veronica Nettles, and composer Augusta Read Thomas at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0764.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_228.tif)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley, cellist Veronica Nettles, and composer Augusta Read Thomas at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0766.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_229.tif)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley, cellist Veronica Nettles, and composer Augusta Read Thomas at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name mezzi soprano Julia Bentley Veronica Nettles cello, composer Augusta Read Thomas.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_230.tif)
- Daniel Bassin conducting flutist Wayla Chambo, violinist Christina Courtin, clarinetist Michael Tumiel, and cellist Sarah Bish in a performance of Augusta Read Thomas's Scat at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0770.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_231.tif)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas shaking hands with conductor Daniel Bassin after a performance of Thomas's Scat at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0771.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_232.tif)
- Mezzo-soprano Julia Bentley and cellist Veronica Nettles after a performance of Bernard Rands's Walcott songs at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0772.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_233.tif)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas shaking hands with cellist Veronica Nettles after a performance of Thomas's Passion prayers at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0773.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_234.tif)
- Pianist Cynthia Bryndis Schilling and cellist Sarah Bish performing Lukas Foss's Capriccio at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0778.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_235.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain conducting a performance of Jacob Druckman's Come around at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0781.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_236.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain conducting a performance of Jacob Druckman's Come around at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0782.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_237.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain conducting a performance of Jacob Druckman's Come around at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name STAGE 1-.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_238.tif)
- Matthew Chamberlain conducting a performance of Jacob Druckman's Come around at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0785.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_239.tif)
- June in Buffalo Performance Institute 2015 faculty and participants, Pei-Lun Tsai, Jonathan Golove, Adam Sherkin, Sarah Bish, Wayla Chambo, Matthew Chamberlain, Anna Whistler, T. J. Borden, Cynthia Bryndis Schilling, Samuel Wells, Eric Huebner, Nicholas Emmanuel, and Benjamin Havey, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0791.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_240.tif)
- June in Buffalo Performance Institute 2015 faculty and participants, Jonathan Golove, Mia Detwiler, Adam Sherkin, Pei-Lun Tsai, Sarah Bish, Wayla Chambo, Anna Whistler, Matthew Chamberlain, Cynthia Bryndis Schilling, T. J. Borden, Samuel Wells, Eric Huebner, Nicholas Emmanuel, Benjamin Havey, Max Fahland, Joe Desotelle, and Daniel Bassin, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0794.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_241.tif)
- June in Buffalo Performance Institute 2015 faculty and participants, Jonathan Golove, Mia Detwiler, Adam Sherkin, Pei-Lun Tsai, Sarah Bish, Wayla Chambo, Anna Whistler, Matthew Chamberlain, Cynthia Bryndis Schilling, T. J. Borden, Samuel Wells, Eric Huebner, Nicholas Emmanuel, Benjamin Havey, Max Fahland, Joe Desotelle, and Daniel Bassin, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0796.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_242.tif)
- June in Buffalo Performance Institute 2015 faculty and participants, Jonathan Golove, Mia Detwiler, Adam Sherkin, Pei-Lun Tsai, Sarah Bish, Wayla Chambo, Anna Whistler, Matthew Chamberlain, Cynthia Bryndis Schilling, T. J. Borden, Samuel Wells, Eric Huebner, Nicholas Emmanuel, Benjamin Havey, Max Fahland, Joe Desotelle, and Daniel Bassin, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0799.tif Venue: Kleinhans Music Hall (Image-file ubmu0074_243.tif)
- Harvey Sollberger playing accordion at a June in Buffalo 2015 concert, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0804.tif Venue: Pausa Art House (Buffalo, N.Y.) (Image-file ubmu0074_244.tif)
- Harvey Sollberger playing accordion at a June in Buffalo 2015 concert, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0806.tif Venue: Pausa Art House (Buffalo, N.Y.) (Image-file ubmu0074_245.tif)
- Harvey Sollberger playing accordion at a June in Buffalo 2015 concert, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0807.tif Venue: Pausa Art House (Buffalo, N.Y.) (Image-file ubmu0074_246.tif)
- Harvey Sollberger playing flute at a June in Buffalo 2015 concert, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0809.tif Venue: Pausa Art House (Buffalo, N.Y.) (Image-file ubmu0074_247.tif)
- Harvey Sollberger playing flute at a June in Buffalo 2015 concert, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Harvey Sollberger flute at Pause art house.tif Venue: Pausa Art House (Buffalo, N.Y.) (Image-file ubmu0074_248.tif)
- Harvey Sollberger playing flute at a June in Buffalo 2015 concert, 2015-06-05, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0819.tif Venue: Pausa Art House (Buffalo, N.Y.) (Image-file ubmu0074_249.tif)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas presenting a lecture at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0821.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_250.tif)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas presenting a lecture at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0825.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_251.tif)
- One image from Olivier Pasquet's video accompanying David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux performed at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0826.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_252.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking with soprano Heather Buck and bass Ethan Herschenfeld at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0841.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_253.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking with soprano Heather Buck and bass Ethan Herschenfeld at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0844.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_254.tif)
- Soprano Heather Buck and bass Ethan Herschenfeld onstage prior to the performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015 with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0846.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_255.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0850.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_256.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0852.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_257.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0853.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_258.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0854.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_259.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0858.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_260.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0860.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_261.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0861.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_262.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_263.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0868.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_264.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0869.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_265.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0872.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_266.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0875.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_267.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0876.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_268.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0879.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_269.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0880.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_270.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0884.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_271.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0888.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_272.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0889.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_273.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0890.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_274.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0891.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_275.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0892.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_276.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0894.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_277.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0895.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_278.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0897.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_279.tif)
- One image from Olivier Pasquet's video accompanying David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux performed at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0900.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_280.tif)
- One image from Olivier Pasquet's video accompanying David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux performed at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0901.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_281.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0906.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_282.tif)